PS E:\factCheckig> python3 main.py 
Initializing Fact-Checking System...
Device set to use cpu

================================================================================
EXAMPLE 1
================================================================================
Transcribing: sample1.wav ...
C:\Users\Hp\AppData\Local\Packages\PythonSoftwareFoundation.Python.3.12_qbz5n2kfra8p0\LocalCache\local-packages\Python312\site-packages\transformers\models\whisper\generation_whisper.py:573: FutureWarning: The input name `inputs` is deprecated. Please make sure to use `input_features` instead.
  warnings.warn(
Due to a bug fix in https://github.com/huggingface/transformers/pull/28687 transcription using a multilingual Whisper will default to language detection followed by transcription instead of translation to English.This might be a breaking change for your use case. If you want to instead always translate your audio to English, make sure to pass `language='en'`.
Extracting claims...
Found 4 claims to verify
Verifying claims...
In what went on to become an extremely awkward moment, US President Donald Trump claimed that Ireland "takes advantage" of the United States while meeting Irish Prime Minister Micheal Martin. When Trump claimed that the European Union "was set up in order to take advantage of the United States," a reporter asked him if that included Ireland which is a part of the EU.

President Donald Trump is hosting Ireland's prime minister, Micheál Martin, for the annual St. Patrick's Day celebration at the White House.

Donald Trump loves the Irish. Do they really have a choice? Ireland's leader survives painful St. Paddy's visit; was not asked to perform Lucky Charms leprechaun jig

President Donald Trump accused Ireland of taking U.S companies via taxation before exchanging shamrock bowls with Irish Taoiseach Micheal Martin at the White House on Wednesday.

The prime minister of Ireland, Micheal Martin, is the latest European leader to visit United States President Donald Trump during his second term in the White House. But the occasion was a ...

Donald Trump's inauguration speech signals significant change for US multinationals with investments in Ireland. The new US President's promise to make the US a "manufacturing nation once ...

He respectfully pointed out to President-elect Trump that the relationship between the United States and Ireland is now a two-way trading relationship, with many jobs created across every State in the United States by Irish companies. He concluded by saying, "He's a businessman. He understands that Irish companies also contribute a huge amount in terms of jobs and investment to the United ...

US President Donald Trump welcomed Irish Prime Minister Micheal Martin to the White House for St. Patrick's Day as tensions ramp up between Washington and the European Union over tariffs.

President Donald Trump welcomed Irish Prime Minister Micheál Martin on Wednesday for the annual St. Patrick's Day celebration at the White House, where he added Ireland to the list of countries ...

Donald Trump has pledged to implement big economic, political and security changes. How is Ireland likely to be affected?
Podcast: Donald Trump says he has personally donated millions to charity in recent years. Rather than debunking his claims, Washington Post reporter David Fahrenthold set out to prove them true ...

Skeptical replies peppered the comment sections of posts claiming Trump personally donated millions to hurricane relief efforts.

Trump frequently matched or supplemented these charitable donations, leading to millions of dollars being given to various organizations. In the celebrity edition of "The Apprentice," Trump raised even more money for charity, directing large sums to hospitals, educational programs, and organizations that support vulnerable populations.

Multiple viral posts claim former President Donald Trump has donated $25 million dollars of his own money to victims of Hurricane Helene.

John Cassidy on Donald Trump's charitable giving in terms of statements by the candidate or on his behalf, and what his foundation's tax returns reveal.

Executive Summary President Donald Trump publicly pledged to return his presidential salary and specific reporting indicates his first quarter paycheck was directed to the Department of Veterans Affairs, though competing accounts and broader reporting have created confusion about other recipients and whether any charities beyond government entities received salary-derived donations [1 ...

Some have won legal relief. Others have been pardoned for their crimes, or benefited from policy changes. But what unites them is donations made to the favoured groups of President Donald Trump.

The Trump campaign organized a fundraiser to support Hurricane Helene victims. But whether he donated millions of his own money is another question.

Donald Trump's Charitable Donations Varied Widely by Year Former president's tax returns report no contributions to charity in 2020 and nearly $1.9 million in 2017

WASHINGTON (AP) — Donald Trump, widely believed to be the wealthiest American ever to run for president, is nowhere among the ranks of the country's most generous citizens, according to an Associated Press review of his financial records and other government filings. Trump has said he donated $102 million worth of cash and land to philanthropic and conservation organizations over the past ...
Two alarming reasons suggest a 33% chance of Donald Trump dying in office, raising concerns about his presidency and its implications.

Obviously! September 2023 Probably the most wild of every Donald Trump death hoax came in 2023, when his own son was the one behind it.

Is President Donald Trump dead? No. Still, many online insist otherwise. Why did these rumors spiral so far out of control?

The president is not dead. Trump spoke live at the White House on Sept. 2. Even as rumors of his death went viral, he had been photographed by news outlets and his Truth Social posts racked up ...

In September 2023, his son Donald Trump Jr.'s X account was hacked, and a hoax post claimed Trump had died and that his son was entering the presidential race.

Rumors claiming Trump died at 79 have gone viral, fueled by his brief public absence, JD Vances remarks, and wild Simpsons theories. But the president was just spotted golfing, alive and well. Heres what really sparked the shocking 'Trump death hoax and why it spread so fast.

This isn't the first false report: in September 2023, Donald Trump Jr.'s X account was hacked, falsely claiming his father had died. Trump quickly refuted it via Truth Social.

A screenshot of what seemed to be a CNN article suggesting the demise of Donald Trump, had been going viral on X. The article titled "Donald Trump dies at 79" has sparked prompts like "Trump is dead" or "Trump died" trending on the social media platform. As soon as the screenshot went viral, chaos ...

Over Labor Day weekend, a wild online rumor falsely said President Donald Trump died. The president is alive. Here's how the viral misinformation spread.

A false announcement about former President Donald Trump's death was posted during a hack of his son's X account.   
A manipulated video of US President Donald Trump appearing to say he would "erase Pakistan" if it attacks India has circulated online as tensions between the nuclear-armed rivals intensified after a deadly attack on tourists in Indian-administered Kashmir. The original video in fact shows Trump talking about the US economy in 2016.

A social media post claims that an accompanying video shows US President Donald Trump threatening to destroy or end Pakistan if it attacks India in the after...

Claim: The viral video shows former U.S. President Donald Trump challenging Pakistan, saying he would destroy the country if it attacks India. Fact: The video is from a September 2016 event where Trump discussed economic reforms at the Economic Club of New York. The original footage contains no such statement. AI detection by HIVE confirmed the video is authentic, but the audio likely AI ...

I know both leaders. There's great tension between Pakistan and India, but there always has been." Also Read: Old Video Of Chinese Military Drill Falsely Shared As Post-Pahalgam Attack Exercise Near Himalayas Conclusion Hence, the viral video showing Donald Trump warning Pakistan against attacking India was found to be manipulated using AI.      

What happened: Pro-India, anti-Pakistan social media users are citing two manipulated videos of U.S. President Donald Trump seemingly stating that he would "destroy" or "erase" Pakistan if it attacked India. The videos are AI deepfakes. Context: In early May 2025, India and Pakistan were on high alert after five militants shot and killed 26 tourists, most of them Indian, in an April 22 ...

AI Audio Is a video of President Trump threatening to "erase Pakistan" if it attacks India authentic? No, that's not true: The video uses old footage of Trump from before he was President and added an AI generated audio track. In the fake audio Trump can also be heard saying he will "warn China" and that he loves "Indian people". The video appeared in an Instagram post (archived here ...

AAP FACTCHECK - A fake video of US President Donald Trump makes it appear as if he threatened to "erase Pakistan" during a speech he made at the Economic Club of New York. Trump did not mention 'Pakistan' or 'India' in the 2016 speech and the clip appears to have been manipulated.

Claim: A video shows US President Donald Trump threatening to destroy Pakistan if it attacked India. Fact: The viral video is digitally manipulated. Trump has consistently taken a neutral stance on tensions between India and Pakistan. Forensic audio analysis and deepfake detection tools confirm that the clip is fabricated.

Vishvas News found in its investigation that the audio of Donald Trump in the viral video is not real and it has been created with the help of AI.

A video showing US President Donald Trump talking about tensions between India and Pakistan is going viral online. "If Pakistan attacks India, I will not sit back, I will destroy Pakistan.

RESULTS (Processed in 18.17s)
Claims analyzed: 4
True: 0 | False: 3 | Uncertain: 1
Errors: 0
Accuracy Score: 0.0%

DETAILED RESULTS:

1. Donald Trump died in 2023.
   Verdict: False (Confidence: high)
Evidence: Two alarming reasons suggest a 33% chance of Donald Trump dying in office, raising concerns about his presidency and its implications.

Obviously! September 2023 Probably the most wild of every Donald...

2. Donald Trump was the president of Ireland.
   Verdict: False (Confidence: high)
Evidence: In what went on to become an extremely awkward moment, US President Donald Trump claimed that Ireland "takes advantage" of the United States while meeting Irish Prime Minister Micheal Martin. When Tru...

3. Donald Trump donated millions to charity.
   Verdict: Uncertain (Confidence: medium)
Evidence: Podcast: Donald Trump says he has personally donated millions to charity in recent years. Rather than debunking his claims, Washington Post reporter David Fahrenthold set out to prove them true ...

S...

4. Donald Trump made a statement about intending to destroy Pakistan in 2025 by attacking Islamabad directly.       
   Verdict: False (Confidence: high)
Evidence: A manipulated video of US President Donald Trump appearing to say he would "erase Pakistan" if it attacks India has circulated online as tensions between the nuclear-armed rivals intensified after a d...