Initializing Fact-Checking System...
Loading image captioning model...
ImageAgent ready.

================================================================================
EXAMPLE 1
================================================================================
[ImageAgent] Caption generated: a woman holding a sign that says vaccines cause autism
Extracting claims...
Found 2 claims to verify
Verifying claims...
This disorder causes problems in social interaction and communication. It also includes limited and repetitive patterns of behavior. The term "spectrum" in autism spectrum disorder refers to the wide range of symptoms and severity. Vaccines do not cause autism.

You may have heard people say that vaccines cause autism. More than 20 rigorous, high-quality studies have found no evidence to support this claim. Yet, it persists, and that can weigh on families trying to make the best decisions about their children's health. We asked the clinical experts at the Child Mind Institute's Autism Center to help us understand the origins of the claim, why it ...

However, no links have been found between any vaccine ingredients and autism. For the CDC notice, go to http://www.cdc.gov/vaccinesafety/concerns/autism/. That autism is a terrible condition for parents and children is not at issue. It is, however, treatable. And it is not caused by vaccines.

Vaccines do not cause autism. YouÆve almost certainly read that before ù but often without a full explanation of how we know it to be true. Here's how we know.

RESULTS (Processed in 29.07s)
Claims analyzed: 2
True: 0 | False: 1 | Uncertain: 1
Errors: 0
Accuracy Score: 0.0%

DETAILED RESULTS:

1. A woman is holding a sign. #break claims into if soething is a claim or not agen
   Verdict: Uncertain (Confidence: medium)
Evidence: Search failed after multiple attempts. Please try again later.

2. The sign contains the text "vaccines cause autism."
   Verdict: False (Confidence: high)
Evidence: This disorder causes problems in social interaction and communication. It also includes limited and repetitive patterns of behavior. The term "spectrum" in autism spectrum disorder refers to the wide ...
